<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Projects on Dreamwalker Collective</title><link>https://dreamwalker.games/projects/</link><description>Recent content in Projects on Dreamwalker Collective</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dreamwalker.games/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tabletop Treasures</title><link>https://dreamwalker.games/projects/tabletop/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreamwalker.games/projects/tabletop/</guid><description>If there&amp;rsquo;s one thing we&amp;rsquo;ve learned while traversing the worlds, it&amp;rsquo;s that there are untold numbers of them &amp;ndash; and that those other worlds need other tools.
So, we&amp;rsquo;ve started compiling a collection for those who traverse the Multiverse. This compendium contains a growing array of profiles, gadgets, maps, items, and more. A veritable treasure trove.</description></item><item><title>FactionFriend Reborn</title><link>https://dreamwalker.games/projects/factionfriendreborn/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreamwalker.games/projects/factionfriendreborn/</guid><description>&lt;p>Founded by a Druidic Ambassador, the Dreamwalker Collective knows the tremendous value of keeping track of where one stands with the numerous factions of Azeroth and beyond. Even from our earliest days, we were not long without &lt;a href="http://www.fizzwidget.com/factionfriend">FactionFriend&lt;/a>, the faction managing gadget created by the wonderful little goblin, &lt;a href="http://www.fizzwidget.com">Gazmik Fizzwidget&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As he so aptly put it:&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>It&amp;rsquo;s amazing the lengths some will go to to win friends. Gaining the trust of furbolg tribes, mushroom men, frost giants, and other organizations of demi-goblinoid races can be a lot of work, and it can be easy sometimes to lose track of one&amp;rsquo;s progress. That&amp;rsquo;s where Fizzwidget Industries comes in! Our newest gadget not only helps you keep tabs on whose respect you&amp;rsquo;re earning, but also how much more you could earn by turning in certain items you&amp;rsquo;re carrying.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>Is it any wonder why we couldn&amp;rsquo;t just let it be relegated to a corner of his workshop, while he is off to someplace unknown, possibly never to return?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We&amp;rsquo;ve picked up the mantle in his stead, keeping one of our most favorite gadgets in working order, and we hope that if &amp;ndash; &lt;em>when&lt;/em> &amp;ndash; he returns, he&amp;rsquo;ll appreciate the care we&amp;rsquo;ve taken of it in his absence.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>